Lebogang Selao

UI designer Frontend Developer

About me

UI designer with 2 years working experience skilled in optimizing work processes to enhance user experience, Frontend Development, App and web Development with Figma, adobe XD, web-flow, HTML, CSS, javascript, React / React native as well as AWC

Projects links

ibottit app

<u>ibottit.com</u>

Brandbook insights

Netflix clone

Twilight Development Center

<u>Github</u>

Figma projects links

ibottit Assets

<u>Airbnb clone</u>

Ibottit Whatsapp app

Certification link

Qualifications

Contact



17 Warbler street, Elspark Germiston, 1428



067 731 3290



lmselao@gmail.com



in

Lebogang Selao Linkedin

WORK EXPERIENCE

Brandbook

Sandton March 2021 - present

Reference

Bakuena Ntshasa CEO, ibottit +27 74 7758396

Software Developer

- Developed ibottit website with webflow
- Developed ibottit insights with javascript to collaborate with clients such as mccain, Unilever, AB-InBev, Beiersdorf.
- Developed ibottit app with react native
- designing ibottit assets with figma
- User support /Client Support queries
- Developed ibottit app on whatsapp text: +1 (844) 265-7988 to test app

BBD

Johannesburg Feb 2020 - May 2021

Reference

Chris McCully Grad master, HR +27 82 176 7194

Junior Software Developer Intern

- HTML, CSS, javascript, React bootcamp
- HTML, CSS, javascript
- UI Design with figma
- UI developed with IOS swift
- Frontend development IOS & swift
- Developed Stakoverflow API app

Bizatelecoms

Sandton March 2012 - Jan 2019

Reference

Justice Setlodi +27 82 051 0423

Computer Software Support

- Chomi website Administrator
- Computer technician
- Chomi website maintenance
- Developed ibottit app with react native
- designing ibottit assets with figma and

EDUCATION

Wethinkcode

Johannesburg Feb 2019 - Nov 2020

Software Engineer

- Figma designs
- AWS Cloud (ELB, databases, ECS, Route 53, billing, IAM roles, API gateway)
- Javascript & React (Tinder clone)
- PHP (Intagram clone)
- C (function library)
- My SQL, Dynamo db
- Project management tools (Srum, Jira)
- Intro to Docker
- Darkly (Web security)

EWC College

Germiston Jan 2008 - Nov 2010

IT and Computer Science

- A+ and N+
- Computer Programming
- Math
- English
- Project management
- system development
- Life Orientation